hervia.com 2012-10-03

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

**By submitting your information you consent to the use of that information as laid out below.**

**1\. Introduction**

For the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998 the ‘Data Controller' for this website is [Hervia Group Limited](http://www.hervia.com/about-us-i1). The privacy and security of our customers is important to us. This privacy policy explains how we use the information we collect about you, how you can instruct us if you prefer to limit the use of that information, and the procedures that we have in place to safeguard your privacy. **2\. The information we collect and how we use it** In order to purchase products or services from us, we need to know your name, address, and email address and various other details. We gather this information to allow us to contact you efficiently and deal with your order. The relevant information is then used by us, and our agents to communicate with you regarding our products and services or as otherwise required. If you wish to register for our Mail service you must provide us with your name and email address. From time to time we may provide the information that you have provided in subscribing to the Mail service or in purchasing products or services through the website to our customer service agencies for research and analysis purposes so that we can monitor and improve the services we provide. We may also wish to provide you with information about special features of our website or any other services or products from Hervia Group and its associated companies that we think may be of interest to you. If you would rather not receive this information, please [contact us](http://www.hervia.com/contact-us-i3) Aside from the matters laid out above, your personal data will not be disclosed to any third party save with your consent.   
**  
**  
**3\. Our use of cookies and other information gathering technologies** Hervia Group Limited employ information gathering technologies for the purposes of collecting information and statistics about the users of this site, but such information will not be used to identify any individual. The purpose of gathering such information is to assist us to analyse the use of the website and revise it for the benefit of our customers by making your visit to the site more efficient and to improve and increase the content found to be most popular. We also employ cookies on this site. Cookies are small text files used on the internet for a variety of purposes. We use cookies to make your use of the website more efficient, for example by saving you the trouble of re-entering information. Although the cookie may provide an automated identification of your computer to our workstation, no personal data is stored in the cookie. You may adjust your computer's settings to block cookies, or to accept them only on confirmation from you. Because of the wide variety of browsers and operating systems used by our customers we cannot provide detailed instructions for this, however your browser should contain details in its help facility. **4\. How we protect your information** The internet is not a secure medium. We have put in place various security measures but you are advised to treat the internet as an insecure medium in all your communications with us. However payments made through this website are handled using secure socket layer technology or other technology which is at least (if not more) secure than that. Your payment information will not be retained by us and will not be disclosed to anyone under any circumstances. **5\. Sale of business** Hervia Group Limited is integrated into any other company or organisation your details may be disclosed to our advisers and any prospective operators and their advisers and will be passed on to the new operators of Hervia Group Limited. **6\. Updating your details** If any of the information that you have provided to Hervia Group Limited changes, for example if you change your email address, please update your details within the my account section of the website. **7\. Your consent** By submitting your information you consent to the use of that information as set out in this policy. If we change our privacy policy we will post the changes on this page, and may place notices on other pages of the website, so that you may be aware of the information we collect and how we use it at all times. We will also email you should you make any changes so that you may consent to our use of your information in that way. Continued use of the service will signify that you agree to any such changes. Owing to the global nature of the internet's infrastructure the information you provide may be temporarily transferred to and stored in countries outside the European Economic Area that do not have similar protections in place regarding your data and its use as set out in this policy whilst in transmission.

**Payment and Security**

Payment can be made online by any credit or debit card, or by Paypal.

Our site uses the latest 128 bit SSL security, complying with and exceeding all necessary security requirements to protect your details. We do not store any sensitive information (card number, etc).

SSL encrypts your order online to avoid any decoding of that information of anyone other than the necessary processing parties. To check the security of your connection, look at the status bar of your browser window after accessing the server. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock then, depending upon your browser, SSL is active. You can also double check by looking at the URL line of your browser - while accessing a secure server the first characters of the address will change from HTTP to HTTPS.
